今晚我要出去  心情大好
I'm going out tonight, I'm feelin' alright
我要好好爽一下
Gonna let it all hang out
放声歌唱  升三个八度
Wanna make some noise, really raise my voice
耶  我要大唱大叫
Yeah, I wanna scream and shout
滴滴啦啦
De-de-de, de-de-de-de-de, uh
不  早安  谢尔顿  和我一起跳舞吧
No.. Morning, Sheldon. Come dance with me.
不要
No.
干嘛不要
Why not?
佩妮  我支持"多个世界"理论
Penny, while I subscribe to
这个理论表明
The "many worlds" theory which pots the existence
在无限个宇宙中存在着
Of an infinite number of sheldons
无限个谢尔顿
In an infinite number of universes,
我向你保证其中没一个"我"是在跳舞的
I assure you that in none of them am I dancing.
那这些"你"里有没有幽默一点的
Are you fun in any of them?
根据推算
The math would suggest
其中有几个"我"是糖娃娃
That in a few I'm a clown made of candy.
但是绝不跳舞
But I don't dance.
行吧  来点法式吐司不
Alright, want some French toast?
今天是燕麦粥日
It's oatmeal day.
这样吧  下个法式吐司日  我给你煮燕麦粥
Tell you what, next French toast day, I'll make you oatmeal.
神啊  你还要在这赖到法式吐司日啊
Dear lord, are you still going to be here on French toast day?
早啊
Morning.
莱纳德  你看啊
Look, Leonard,
佩妮烤了法式吐司
Penny made French toast.
抱歉我还没给她你的用餐日程表
Sorry I haven't given her your schedule yet.
那是个iCal[Apple电子日程表]下载啊
It's an iCal download.
她可以直接下到手机里的
She can put it right in her phone.
而且我想咱们说好了的
And I thought we agreed
你们只在她那儿行房事
That you'd have your conjugal visits in her apartment.
是说好了  但是现在是特殊情况
We did, but there were extenuating circumstances.
我明白了
I see.
她浑身的傻气
Did her abysmal housekeeping skills
终于被她那盖世的家务活能力打压下去了是吗
Finally trump her perkiness?
不  是她的床有点散架了
No, her bed kind of... Broke.
这是不太可能的
That doesn't seem likely.
她的床的构造很结实
Her bed's of sturdy construction.
就算多承重一个
Even the addition of a second
正常体型的人类也不会引致其床架松动的
Normal size human being wouldn't cause a structural failure,
更别提像你这样的小雏形人了
Much less a homunculus such as yourself.
小雏形人
A homunculus?
功能健全的迷你型人类
Perfectly formed miniature human being.
你这我的小宝贝雏形人
Oh, you're my little homunculus.
别这样
Don't do that.
抱歉
Sorry.
好啦  谁要普通糖浆谁要肉桂糖浆呀
Okay, who wants syrup and who wants cinnamon sugar?
我要燕麦粥
I want oatmeal.
行啊
Yes, well
我想要个室友不是大混蛋的男朋友
I want a boyfriend whose roommate isn't a giant pain in the ass.
这个愿望很快就能实现了
I'm sure that will happen soon enough.
但我还是要燕麦粥
But in the meantime, I still want oatmeal.
得了  我投降
You know what, I give up.
怎么会有他这种人
He's impossible.
怎么会没有  我就是存在的
I can't be impossible, I exist.
我相信你想说的是
I believe what you meant to say is,
"我投降  这种人几乎是不存在的"
"I give up, he's improbable."
谢尔顿  你真得换个方式
Sheldon, you really need to find a better way
和佩妮相处了
Of dealing with penny.
那我该怎么做
What am I supposed to do--
在礼拜一吃法式吐司吗
Eat french toast on a Monday?
这种情况才是不存在的
Now, that would be impossible.
我只是说  你想抓苍蝇的话得用蜂蜜
I'm just saying, you can catch more flies with honey
而不是醋
Than with vinegar.
你用粪粪还能抓更多呢
You can catch even more flies with manure.
你到底想说什么
What's your point?
这个...
It's a...
天  还挺香的呢
Boy, that does smell good.
太遗憾了  今儿就是礼拜一
Too bad it's Monday.
生活大爆炸第三季第三集
我们经理基姆去休产假了
Okay, Kim the night manager went on maternity leave
她老公叫桑迪
And her husband's name is Sandy, right?
然后
So get this--
顶她班的是一个叫桑迪的女人
Her replacement is a woman named Sandy
而她老公叫基姆
Whose husband's name is Kim.
-哇啊  -是啊
- Wow!  - I know!
这什么概率哦
What are the odds?
很好算嘛
Easily calculable.
先找到几对双方都取中性名字的
We begin by identifying a set of married couples
已婚夫妇
With unisex names.
然后剔除那些不适合
We then eliminate those unqualified
从事餐饮工作的
For restaurant work--
比如说年老的  坐牢的  残疾的
The aged, the imprisoned and the limbless, for example,
-再然后就  -谢尔顿
- Next we look at... - Sheldon--
这是一个奇妙的巧合
It's an amazing coincidence.
就这样了行吗
Can we leave it at that?
对不起
I'm sorry.
喔佩妮  你们奶酪蛋糕工厂就好像是巫婆们开的
Ooh, Penny. It's as if the cheese-cake factory is run by witches.
喔谢尔顿  别以为我不会揍你
Ooh, Sheldon, it's as if you don't think I'll punch you.
行啦  你俩  别吵了
Come on, you guys, let it go.
哼  随便吧
Fine, whatever.
你吃完了吗
Are you finished?
谢了
Well, thank you.
多么体贴
How thoughtful.
你要吃巧克力吗
Would you like a chocolate?
好啊
Um, yeah, sure.
多谢啦
Thanks.
这算什么
What was that?
你让我对佩妮好点的
You said be nice to Penny.
我觉得给别人喂巧克力
I believe offering chocolate to someone
能够符合"好"的定义
Falls within the definition of nice.
没错
It does.
但就我观察  你这人不符合
But in my experience, you don't.
何瑞修  宇宙间无奇不有
There are more things in heaven and earth, Horatio,
不是你的哲学全能梦想得到的[哈姆雷特 第一幕;第五景]
Than are dreamt of in your philosophy
这才是你嘛
Now that's you
讨厌而且让人难以忍受
Obnoxious and insufferable.
日居者们  你们好啊
What's going on, day dwellers?
KISS[美重金属乐队]粉丝团也废除了"不许问不许说"[美军处理同性恋旧政策]吗
Oh, man, did the kiss army repeal "don't ask, don't tell"?
不是
No.
我和拉杰要去好莱坞的哥特夜总会
Raj and I are going to a goth club in Hollywood
和夜猫子一起玩儿
To hang with the night people.
有人想一起去吗
Anybody want to come along?
你真要这样上街吗
Oh, wow, you're actually going out like that?
不不
No, no.
我要这样上街
I'm going out like this...
霍华德  你做了些什么
Howard, what did you do?
这叫纹身袖
They're called tattoo sleeves.
看
Look.
我在网上买的  拉杰也买了一身
I go them online! Raj got a set, too..
帅死了  是吧
Fantastic, right?
穿上它  就能和前卫女孩
Put them on, have hot sex with some freaky girl
发生韵事  脱下他
With her business pierced, take them off,
我依旧是个恪礼守节的犹太人
I can still be buried in a jewish cemetery.
知道吗
You know, I've always wanted
我一直都想去哥特夜总会
To go to a goth nightclub.
真的吗
Really?
才怪呢
Bazinga!
没有人能察觉到我的玩笑  对吧
None of you ever see my practical jokes coming, do you?
你们俩去吗
Okay, how about you two?
我还带了几个纹身袖
Look, I've got some extra tatoo sleeves.
你带那么多干什么
Why are you carrying extras?
万一被哪个女人的乳环刮破了好有个替换呀
In case I snag one on someone's nipple ring.
我们就不去了
Uh, yeah, I think we'll pass.
你现在就得"妻管严"了吗
Oh, is the missus speaking for the couple now?
这件事  肯定她说了算
In this case, you bet she is.
是啊  她很强势  他受压迫
Yes, she's pushy, and yes, he's whipped,
但是不能这么说
But that's not the expression.
快走  我要去沃尔格林药店
Come on, I want to stop at walgreens
再多买几支眼线笔
And pick up some more eyeliner.
他们在夜总会要被揍了
They're gonna get beaten up at that club.
我看他们在药店就会被揍
They're gonna get beaten up at walgreens.
抱歉  谢尔顿
Oh, sorry, Sheldon.
我差点坐在你的专座上
I almost sat in your spot.
是吗  我都没注意
Did you? I didn't notice.
给你块巧克力吧
Have a chocolate.
谢谢
Thank you.
我觉得我们很适合这里
I think we're fitting quite nicely.
要是你不喝低度啤酒就更好了
It did help if you weren't drinking light beer.
喝伏特加和蔓越莓果汁就显得比我更有哥特风格吗
What's so gothic about vodka and cranberry juice?
是啊  这看起来像在饮血
Hello? It looks like blood.
你没去看我发给你的
Did you even read the "wiki how" link
手把手学哥特风格的WikiHow链接吗
I sent you on being goth?
没  我自己的东西还看不玩呢
No, I'm behind on my wiki-reading.
我正在读约翰·格里沙姆[法律惊悚小说《掮客》作者]
I'm kind of on a John Grisham kick right now.
什么
What?
我看完了《绝对机密》
I finished reading The Pelican Brief
我太喜欢了  已经完全身临其境了
And loved it so much, I dived right into the client.
他本身就是个律师
He was a lawyer himself,
所以他的小说内容的准确性和娱乐性都很强
So his novels are accurate as well as entertaining.
要记住  我们是浪荡子  暗夜之子
Just remember we are lost boys, children of the night.
好的   浪荡子  暗夜之子
Great. Lost boys, children of the night.
明白了
Got it.
能帮忙把小吃递过来吗
Can you pass the chex mix please?
谢谢
Thank you.
我们是浪荡子
We are lost boys.
是吗
Good for you.
其实我比他更放浪
I'm actually much more lost than he is.
纹身不错
Nice ink.
谢谢
Thanks.
能请两位小姐喝点东西吗
Can we buy you ladies a drink?
两杯低度啤酒
Two light beers.
低度啤酒吗  "WiliHow"该把这个写进去
Light beers. "Wiki how" about that?
你们叫什么
What's your names?
-我叫霍华德  拉杰  -我是贝萨妮
-I'm Howard. Raj. -I'm Bethany.
很高兴见到你   贝萨妮
Nice to meet you, Bethany.
很高兴
Yes, very nice.
我也是
Nice to meet you, too.
我叫莎拉
I'm Sarah.
反正也没人关心
Not that anyone cares.
两位小姐喜欢看约翰·格里沙姆的小说吗
Do either of you ladies enjoy the novels of John Grisham?
这动画片叫什么来着
What's this cartoon called again?
恶魔武士
Oshikuru: Demon samurai.
恶魔武士不是动画片
Demon it's not a cartoon.
是动漫
It'anime.
动漫
Anime.
高中时有个女生叫安娜·梅(Anime和Anna May谐音)
You know, I knew a girl in high school named Anna May.
安娜·梅·弗莱彻
Anna May Fletcher.
她天生单鼻孔
She was born with one nostril.
她后来的整鼻手术很失败
Then she had this bad nose job
最后竟然弄成了三个鼻孔
And basically wound up with three.
你现在经常混在这儿了
You're here a lot now.
我话太多了吗
Oh, am I talking too much?
抱歉  我不说了
I'm sorry. Zip.
谢谢
Thank you.
吃块巧克力吧
Chocolate?
好的
Yes please.
基姆 你好
Oh. Hey, Kim.
请你稍等一下
You know what,hold on.
我到楼道里去接电话
Let me take this in the hall.
你绝对想不到他们找谁来接替你的工作
You'll never guess who they got to replace you at work.
我知道你在干什么了
Okay, I know what you're doing.
真的吗
Really?
你在用巧克力做正面教法
Yes, you're ung chocolates as positive reinforcement
对你认为良好的行为进行奖励
For what you consider correct behavior.
真聪明
Very good.
来块巧克力吗
Chocole?
我不想要什么巧克力
No, I don't want any chocolate!
谢尔顿
Sheldon,
你不能拿我女朋友当实验鼠一样对待
You can't train my girlfend like a lab rat.
事实证明  我可以
Actually, it turns out I can.
你不应该这么做
well, you shouldn't.
莱纳德  就是没法让你满意  是吧
There's just no pleasing you, is there, Leonard?
你不满意
You weren't happy
我之前那样对她
With my previous approach to dealing with her,
所以我决定根据桑代克和B.F.斯金纳的理论
So I decided to employ operant conditioning techniques,
采取操作性条件反射的办法
Building on the works of thorndike and B.F. Skinner.
下周的这个时候
By this time next week,
我相信我能让她从水池里一跃而出
I believe I can have her jumping out of a pool,
用鼻子平衡塑料气球
Balancing a beach ball on her nose
不行  这一套必须打住
No, this has to stop now.
我不是真的建议让她从水池里跳出来
I'm not suggesting we really make her jump out of a pool.
我以为你该听出了我的"才怪了"
I thought the "bazinga" was implied.
咱们不过是调整她个性
We're just tweaking her personality.
用另一种说法  就是把那些粗糙表面磨磨光
Sanding off the rough edges, if you will.
不行  你不能磨佩妮
No. You're not sanding Penny.
你是说不许我使用
Are you saying that I am forbidden
能让改进我们生活的
From applying a harmless, scientifically valid protocol
无害的科学有效的正常手段
That will make our lives better?
是的  我不许
Yes. You're forbidden.
坏莱纳德
Bad Leonard.
那你们俩是做什么的
So, what do you guys do?
就是些  哥特东西喽
Oh, you know, goth stuff.
哥特杂志喽  哥特音乐喽
Goth magazines, goth music.
哥特食品喽
Goth food.
什么哥特食品
What's goth food?
呃  黑焦三文鱼?
Uh. Blackened salmon?
不是  我是问你们的工作
No, I meant what do you do for jobs?
我们是科学家
Oh, we're scientists.
当然  是黑科学的
Yeah, you know, the dark sciences.
什么是黑科学
What are the dark sciences?
我们
We...
我是个天体物理学家
Well, I am an astrophysicist,
很多工作都要在晚上进行
And a lot of that takes place at night.
那时候也有吸血鬼呀
When there are vampires
僵尸呀什么的到处乱跑
And miscellaneous undead out and about.
听起来很酷啊
That sounds really cool.
真的吗  好吧  要是你喜欢宇宙那类的
Does it? Okay. If you like space stuff,
我设计国际太空站的部分呢
I design components for the international space station,
在太空里
Which is in space.
你肯定知道  那里没人能听到你喊叫
Where, as I'm sure you know, no one can hear you scream.
那么  两位女士是做什么的
So, what do you gals do?
我在盖普服装店
I work at the gap.
真的  可真有趣  我曾经去过盖普啊
Really? How about that? I've been to the gap.
我也去过
I've been there, as well.
我喜欢你们那种有小口袋的T恤衫
I like your t-shirts with the little pocket.
我也在那儿上班  反正也没人关心
I work the, too. Not that anyone cares.
这地方真无聊
You know, this place is boring.
可不  咱们去别的地方开心开心吧
Yeah why don't we go somewhere else and have some fun?
好啊
Okay.
当然  我们喜欢开心
Sure we like fun.
我们是开心的人
We are fun people.
又黑暗又开心
Dark and fun.
来吧  我知道一个地方你们肯定喜欢
Come on. I know a place you'll really dig.
你带来黑色避孕套吗
Did you bring the black condoms?
就在腰包包里啦
In my fanny pack.
走吧
Let's go.
现在高兴了
Are you happy now?
没有特别高兴
Not particularly
天啊  她没有吧
My god, she didn't!
她究竟在说什么要这么久
What could she possibly be talking about for so long?
显然  在芝士蛋糕厂做招待
Obviously, waitressing at the cheesecake factory
是个复杂的社会经济性活动
Is a complex socioeconomic activity
而且需要相当多的研究与计划
That requires a great deal of analysis and planning.
才怪了
"bazinga."
知道么  采用
You know, using positive
正面鼓励式方法  我能在一个星期之内
Reinforcement techniques, I could train that behavior
让她改变这个恶习
Out of her in a week.
不
No.
要是你让我用负面鼓励法
If you let me use negative reinforcement,
睡觉前我就能做到
I can get it done before we go to bed.
你不能用水喷她的脸
You're not squirting her in the face with water.
当然不
No, of course not.
我说的是十分轻微的电击法
We're talking very mild electric shocks.
连组织损伤都不会有
No tissue damage whatsoever.
别想了
Forget it.
你不可能告诉我
Oh, come on. You can't tell me
给你打造一个更好的女朋友
That you're not intrigued out the possibility
让你一点都不动心
Of building a better girlfriend.
我没有
I'm not.
佩妮的个性 好的和坏的
Well, and Penny's qualities, both good and bad,
合成了她这个人
Are what make her who she is.
你是说  比如那个让人无法忍受的尖笑声
You mean, like that high-pitched, irritating laugh?
你就不想希望一个低嗓门的笑声吗
You wouldn't prefer a throaty chuckle?
不许你改变佩妮的笑声
You're not changing how Penny laughs.
那才是荒诞呢
No, that would be incongruous.
我打算把她的声音整体降低
I was going to lower the whole voice
到一个令人愉快的音区
To a more pleasing register.
对不起啦  伙计
Ugh. Sorry, guys.
那丫头是个怪物
That girl is freaky.
再说一遍
Come again?
怪物
Freaky.
Freaky?
怪物
Ah, freaky.
吃块巧克力吧
Have a chocolate.
谢谢
Thank you.
你真打算破坏你的身体
Are you seriously going to damage your body
就为了有可能吊上一个
Just for the possibility you could have cheap sex
在酒吧里遇到的马子?
With a strange girl you met in a bar?
当然
Yeah!
你妈妈会怎么说
What is your mother going to say?
她根本看不到那里
She's not going to see it.
她现在量我体温都是放嘴里的
She takes my temperature orally now.
霍华德  你打算要什么样的
What are you going to get, Howard?
我不知道该选
Well, I can't really decide
尖叫魔鬼  骇人小头骨
Between a screaming devil, this mean little skull,
或是青蛙柯米特
Or kermit the frog.
青蛙柯米特
Kermit the frog? You know.
你好  我在霍华德的屁股上
Hi-ho. I'm on Howard's butt.
刺个骇人小头骨
Get the mean little skull,
我会让它笑起来
And I'll see if I can make him smile.
请给我刺一个骇人小头骨
Yeah, I'd like the mean little skull, please.
你要什么  拉杰
What are you going to get, Raj?
像我这种运气  肝炎差不多
With my luck, hepatitis.
好了  我们开始
Okay, here we go.
只擦了点酒精棉花
That's just rubbing alcohol.
我知道  但凉凉的
I know, but it was cold.
我在放图案
I'm putting on the stencil.
放完后怎么做
What comes after the stencil
够了  到此为止
Okay, that's it.
不刺针  不痛苦  不纹身
No needle. No pain. No tattoo.
小事一桩而已  你又不是没纹过
What's the big deal? You've done this before.
我没纹过
No, I haven't.
看
Look.
抱歉  我骗了你们
I'm sorry. I'm a fraud.
他是个骗子
He's a fraud.
我们都说谎了
We're both frauds.
我不是已经说过了吗
Yeah, I think I covered that.
我是在总结
But I was summing up.
我们不是哥特  我们只是普通人
We're not Goth. We're just...guys.
非常  非常聪明的人
Very, very smart guys.
那你们一直在骗人
So you were totally scamming us?
是的
Yes.
要是你想离开再也不想见到我们
And I wouldn't blame you if you
我也不会怪你
Walked out of here and never wanted to see us again.
除非  这突如其来的坦率
Unless, of course,our bold honesty
给我们增添了无限魅力
Has suddenly made us attractive
怎么样
Huh? Huh? Anything?
我要走了
I'm leaving.
我也要走了  反正也没人关心
I'm leaving, too. Not that anyone cares.
等回去说起此事时  要编个不一样的结局
When we tell this story, let's end it differently.
你在想什么  是不是还要来一段歌舞
What are you thinking? Maybe a big musical number?
我弄点热牛奶就进去睡了
Well, I'm going to make some warm milk and then turn in.
我相信如果你们打算
I trust if you two are planning on engaging
亲热的话
In amorous activities,
会尽量小声点的
You'll keep the decibel level to a minimum.
当然
Of course.
谢谢
Thank you.
味道真好
Mmm. These are so good.
难以置信
Unbelievable.
怎么了
What?
我刚在想
I-I was just thinking
我们也该进房睡了
We should probably turn in, too.
我的新床送来了
Well, you know, my new bed got delivered. If you come over
如果你过来把它组装好  就能睡在我那里了
And put it together, you can stay at my place.
是吗  但得花不少时间  而且现在有点晚了
Really? That's a lot of work, and it's kind of late.
但那样我们就不用小声了
Yeah, but if we stay there, we won't have tbe quiet.
我们走
Let's go.
有趣
Interesting.
在修正行为方面  性爱比巧克力更有效
Sex works even better than chocolate to modify behavior.
不知道有没有人研究过这点
I wonder if anyone else has stumbled onto that.
等等  这个故事怎么样
Okay, wait. How about this?
有四个哥特女孩
We say there were four goth girls.
酒吧里有两个女孩  她们还有两个朋友
The two girls in the club have two friends.
不错  不错
I like it, I like it.
虽然她们是哥特  但她们的味道香吗
Did they smell good despite their goth-like nature?
这有什么关系
What's that got to do with the story?
加上嗅觉的描述  我觉得比较真实
Engaging my olfactory sense helps make it real for me.
好吧  她们闻起来香香的
Fine, they smelled good
确实  就像茉莉和金银花
Oh, they did. Like jasmine and honeysuckle
无所谓
Whatever.
她们手拉手  对我们疯狂的
And then they held hands and did a sexy, demonic
做下流动作
Hokey pokey for us.
不不  先让我把故事说完
No, no. Ok, let me just say my story all the way through
你再说你的  然后我们再选
And then you can say yours, and then we'll pick.
抱歉  你继续说
I'm sorry. Go on.
我们去纹了身
Okay. We got tattoos,
-然后四个女孩带我们到她们的住所  -但我们没有纹身
- And then the four girls took us to their place - But we don't have tattoos.E.
万一有人要看纹身  怎么办
What if someone asks to see our tattoos?
我们就说纹在了非常私密的部位
We say they're in a very intimate area.
我们太坏了  不是吗
Oh, we're bad boys, aren't we?
就是  就是
Right, right.
再回头说她们的住所
So, we go back to their place
最后我们六个人倒在热气腾腾的浴缸中
And then the six of us end up in a hot tub.
但我们刚纹了身
But we just got tattos.
我们不怕细菌感染吗
Wouldn't we be concerned about bacterial infection?
对  那不要浴缸这段了
True. Okay. Forget the hot tub.
重点是我们都和火辣的哥特女孩亲热
The point is, we each had a ménage with sexy goth girls.
今晚太棒了
What a great night.
是啊
Yeah.
明晚去乡村酒吧碰运气吗
Hey, want to try a country bar tomorrow night?
也许我们能钓上几个牛仔女孩
Maybe we'll get lucky with some sexy cowgirls.
很有可能
Could happen.
不知道她们闻起来什么味道
I wonder how they smell.